**ASUS Privacy Policy****/ ASUS EU Data Act Policy** 
=====================================================

ASUSTek Computer Inc. and its affiliated entities (“ASUS”, “we, “our, or “us”) are dedicated to protecting your privacy/ data and complying with privacy/ data laws. Please find the below general introduction of ASUS Privacy Policy (**Part 1**) and ASUS EU Data Act Policy (**Part 2**) regarding our practices of privacy/ data protection.  

**\*Pa****rt 1: ASUS Privacy Policy:**
--------------------------------------

The ASUS Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”), along with any other privacy notices related to specific products and services, explains how we collect, use, and safeguard your personal data online and offline. The Privacy Policy also details who we may share or disclose the collected personal data with.

If you are a child, you can only use ASUS products and services if your parent (or guardian) has read and agreed to our Privacy Policy and consents to providing your personal data to ASUS.

### **1\. How ASUS collects and uses data**

 **This paragraph explains how ASUS products and services may collect and use your data.**

When you use or interact with ASUS products and services, such as ASUS computers, software, official websites, and customer support services, we may need to collect specific personal data from you for certain purposes. The following is a general overview, not an exhaustive list, of how ASUS may collect and use your data. It's important to note that we only collect specific personal data based on the ASUS products and services you use. The type of personal data collected varies depending on the nature of each product and service. Additionally, in some countries, to ensure we don't wrongly collect or use children's personal data, you may be required to provide your date of birth for age check or your parent's (or guardian's) contact information for consent. Moreover, when you use ASUS products and services, we may also collect anonymous data that cannot directly or indirectly identify you.

You have the choice not to provide the personal data requested by ASUS when using our products and services. However, if you opt not to share your personal data, ASUS may be unable to provide the corresponding products and services or respond to your inquiries.

#### 1.1 ASUS collection of personal data

Personal data refers to any information that could identify you, either directly or indirectly, including details like your name, email address, and IP address. ASUS may collect the following personal data with your prior consent or with legitimate grounds.

(1) When you sign up for an ASUS/ROG account, we may collect the registration data you provided following Section 8.1.1, including your email address, country/region, and date of birth (required in some countries). If you use your social media account (like Facebook, Google, Apple ID or Microsoft account) to sign up, the social media provider may share data from your account (such as email address of your social media account) to ASUS based on your consent.

Additionally, when you log into your ASUS/ROG account on the ASUS official website (Route: Visit ASUS official website [http://www.asus.com/entry.htm](http://www.asus.com/entry.htm)→find “LOGIN” on the upper-right side of the website→insert the E-mail address and password you registered for ASUS/ROG account find your data under “My Account”), you can optionally add extra personal data to your profile (like your picture, gender, address, or profession) and access associated products and services (such as ASUS product registration by entering your product serial number and purchase information, your forum posts and uploaded content).

(2) When you buy a product or service from the ASUS official online store at our official website, for order management or to provide ASUS online store-related services, we collect your name, shipping/billing address, contact info (such as email and phone number), and order details. For some countries where ASUS official online stores are operated by our authorized resellers, the above data will also be collected by those resellers to fulfill your purchase orders with them. For more information about how they collect and use your personal data through ASUS official online store, please consult their privacy policies.

(3) If you request customer services (such as a repair or an inquiry about ASUS products or services), we may collect your name, contact info (such as email and phone number), shipping address, country, product identifiers (such as serial number), product purchase information (such as a copy of your proof of purchase to calculate or evaluate your warranty period), fail-log files in your product and your VAT number or Tax Code for invoice issuance (if the services incur any costs).

(4) When you enter our events or campaigns, we may collect your name, contact info, submitted content (such as posts, reviews, or pictures), product identifiers (such as serial number), product purchase information (such as a copy of your proof of purchase), and additional personal data if you win or receive giveaways, such as a shipping address for the delivery of physical giveaways, and your residential address, ID or passport number and its copy for tax declaration purpose. The collected data items will vary depending on the types of events or campaigns you join. Moreover, for certain events that offer cashback, you may need to provide your bank account information for wire-transfer purposes.

(5) When you use our healthcare products and services, we may collect health-related data like age, gender, height, weight, body temperature, heart rate, blood pressure, and daily activity information.

(6) When you use ASUS products and services, we may collect log data like IP Address and DDNS name for internet or network connection and providing services. We may also collect serial number, MAC Address, WiFi MAC Address, IMEI number, CPU ID, and other unique identifiers to perform and enhance the functions of ASUS products and services.

(7) We may collect location data associated with ASUS products and services, such as GPS signal, nearby WiFi access points, cell towers, country, city, time zone, latitude, longitude and country settings on your product to perform and enhance the functions of ASUS products and services.

(8) When you contact ASUS via phone calls, an online chat, a website form, or an email, we may collect voice, video, and communication records. When you walk-in our physical locations such as ASUS Royal Club repair stations, security cameras may record your image at ASUS locations. Additionally, when using robot-related products, we may collect voice instructions and video records containing your images of your home environment to perform the functions. These records may contain personal data.

(9) When you contact us through business channels (such as filling in our business or public-relations contact forms, joining business partners’ portals or reward programs), we may collect your name, business contact information (such as your business email and phone number) and your company information.

(10) When you use ASUS products and services in online environment, we need to use your IP address for internet connection purpose.

(11) When you activate ASUS products, for our legitimate interests, we may collect activation data through your products, such as serial number, IP address and activation time.

#### 1.2 How ASUS uses your personal data

We might use your personal data for the following purposes. It's important to clarify that ASUS does not sell your personal data.

(1) To perform the functions of ASUS products and services.

(2) To evaluate and enhance the performance and quality of ASUS products and services.

(3) To gather customer feedback and analyze user experiences for developing and evaluating new products and services.

(4) To complete the sign-up process for ASUS/ROG accounts and access associated services, such as product registration and ASUS forums.

(5) To facilitate delivery services (such as delivering purchased products), provide order status updates, and issue invoices.

(6) To process and fulfill subscriptions, including ASUS marketing emails or newsletters, to keep you informed about the latest ASUS news, promotions, and events. You can unsubscribe at any time.

(7) To send important notifications and updates, such as software updates, security notices, and communications about changes to terms, conditions, and policies. Opting out of these is not possible due to their importance.

(8) To verify your identity, manage event or campaign entries and rewards, contact you for related matters, provide cashback, declare tax, and offer shuttle services or insurance when needed for events or campaigns.

(9) For healthcare-related products and services, to assist with recording, analyzing, modifying, and storing data, including body data and daily activities. Support is provided for editing and accessing data and activity results when shared with your designated person (such as family, caregivers, or health care professionals).

(10) To deliver customer support services, handle product repair requests, respond to questions, maintain business cooperation, and conduct customer care and satisfaction surveys for user experience analysis. Voice, video, and communication records may be collected for access control and protection of rights and interests, especially when contacting ASUS or visiting physical premises like ASUS Royal Club repair stations and ASUS offices. Voice and video records may also be collected for ASUS robot-related products and services to perform its functions.

(11) To provide personalized marketing services, including using third-party cookies to offer marketing communications and advertising that we believe may interest you, or recommend services based on your use of ASUS products and services.

(12) Any other purposes that you agree to beforehand.

(13) To process your internet connection when you use ASUS products and services in online environment.

(14) Under our legitimate interests, to facilitate our product operation and planning purposes (such as planning for allocation of repair parts) and to calculate the warranty period of your products by using product activation data.

#### 1.3 ASUS collection and usage of anonymous data

Anonymous data refers to information that cannot directly or indirectly pinpoint your identity, like details about the product you're using, the software version, and the invoice date. When you use ASUS products and services, we might collect this type of anonymous data from you and use it for various purposes. Additionally, if this anonymous data gets linked to your personal data mentioned earlier, we will handle it with the same level of protection and care as we do with personal data.

(1) Information related to your use of ASUS products and services includes log data like your product model name, brand, type, manufacturer, part number, hardware details (like CPU and motherboard), operating system, factory settings, activation time, firmware information (such as firmware version) and firmware update details, memory and storage size, ROM-related data (type, version, build fingerprint, build description), camera resolution, screen settings, product color, telecom and network connection details, network status, telephony logs, standby status, crash history, preferred interface, browser type, version, language settings, diagnosis and usage data, user behavior, GPS and WiFi version, system status (battery, CPU, RAM usage, and local time), numbers and time of product boot-ups and security events.

(2) Data related to your use and interaction with ASUS applications and software, including but not limited to application and software names and versions, installation and uninstallation times, login and logout times, usage frequency and numbers, open and close times, preferred application and software categories, usage behavior settings, update version and result, and hotkeys for specific functions on computers (such as Shift + spacebar keys for converting characters to half-width/full-width forms and the arrow/Tab/Enter keys for selecting words and navigating menus).

(3) When you request certain customer support services (for example, product repairs) or participate in events, we collect purchase information for ASUS products and services, such as the purchase date and reseller's name.

### **2\. Retention of your personal data**

**This paragraph introduces how long ASUS retains your personal data.**

We will keep your personal data only for the limited period needed to achieve the goals stated in this Privacy Policy, unless the law allows or requires a longer duration. For instance, we may retain your ASUS/ROG Account member registration data until your membership is cancelled. For customer service data, we may retain your data for customer relationship management for a reasonable period. To comply with tax laws or other regulations, we might keep your information (such as your order information at ASUS official online store) for the period specified by such laws. In cases where governments or the judiciary request data for investigations or legal matters, we may retain your personal data for an extended period.

### **3\. To whom ASUS may disclose your personal data**

**This paragraph explains when ASUS may share your personal data with third parties under limited circumstances and purposes.**

We won't share your personal data with anyone else, unless one of the following exceptions applies:

#### 3.1 Your Consent

We will only share or disclose your personal data to other third parties if you give your permission beforehand.

#### 3.2 Service Providers and Partners

We may share necessary parts of your personal data with our service providers who provide services for us or on our behalf, or with partners who processes your personal data to fulfill services under their own names. For example, marketing agencies help us with promotional activities, forwarder companies handle the delivery of products, advertising campaign providers analyze data for targeted advertisements and marketing communications based on third-party cookies, customer service providers assist with support services like product repairs, call center assistance, and online chat services, and payment-related companies process your billing or conduct payment fraud detection. These service providers and partners are only allowed to use your personal data as per our instructions and/or for the purposes outlined here. ASUS guarantees that all our service providers and partners strictly adhere to the Privacy Policy.

#### 3.3 For legal, protection, security purposes

We might disclose or share necessary parts of your personal data to third parties for legal or security reasons, including:

(1) If it is needed under the laws or regulations, or by government or legal authorities where we consider the request has a valid legal basis, to proceed with legal process, or to prevent fraud or other unlawful activities.

(2) To safeguard the rights, property, or safety of ASUS, our service providers, customers, or the public, as allowed or required by law.

### **4\. Cross-border processing of your personal data** 

**This paragraph explains how ASUS may transfer your personal data to other countries. We strive to follow the privacy laws and regulations in those countries.**

When providing your personal data with ASUS, you understand and agree that ASUS and its affiliated entities or service providers and partners may transfer, store, use, or process your personal data in a country different from yours. These actions regarding your personal data are bound by the Privacy Policy and by the relevant laws on privacy protection and personal data security.

### **5\. Cookies and similar technologies** 

**This paragraph explains how ASUS and third parties use cookies and similar technologies in ASUS products and services, as well as how you can control your cookie settings.**

 Cookies are small text files placed on your devices to help us customize your experience with ASUS products and services. ASUS and our third-party partners use cookies and similar technologies to help deliver those products and services to you. When you access any of our websites under the ASUS domain (including microsites and versions specific to certain countries/regions), those ASUS websites may employ some or all of the following cookies and similar technologies. The types of cookies and similar technologies we use may vary across different websites.

#### 5.1 How we use Cookies

(1) To enhance and improve your online experiences, we use the following essential cookies in ASUS products and services:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Function | Example |
| Sign-up and authentication | We use cookies to save your unique sign-up ID number and authentication data on your devices. These cookies enable you to navigate through different pages within ASUS products and services without needing to log in again during subsequent visits. |
| Storing your preferences and settings | We use cookies to save your preferences and settings on your devices, such as your chosen language, location, or fonts. Storing these settings in cookies means we don't need to reapply them every time you visit our products and services. |
| User-input function | We use cookies to temporarily save the information you enter on ASUS products and services. For instance, when you're shopping in the ASUS official online store at our official website, these cookies help remember the chosen product, the quantity you selected, and any other data you entered. |
| Security | We use cookies to enhance the security of your online activities. For instance, when you buy our products on the ASUS official online store at our official website, we may store your IP address to help us to confirm that the user placing the order is the same as the one logged into the ASUS official online store. |
| Load balancing function | We use cookies to ensure stable browsing experiences on our websites through load-balancing functions. |

(2) For analytical purposes and to offer you personalized advertising services and other functions, we use the following cookies to enhance your experiences when using ASUS products and services: 

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Function | Example |
| Analytics & Advertising cookies | We use cookies to track the duration and frequency of your visits to ASUS products and services, as well as the specific parts or features you visit the most, such as Google Tag Manager, Google Analytics provided by Google Inc. ([https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en)), CrazyEgg cookie provided Crazy Egg, Inc. ([https://www.crazyegg.com/cookies](https://www.crazyegg.com/cookies)), Matomo cookie by InnoCraft Ltd ([https://matomo.org/privacy-policy/](https://matomo.org/privacy-policy/)). This information helps us analyze the performance and functionality of ASUS products and services, allowing us to enhance performance and introduce new features, functions, and services When you browse our websites, these cookie tools may collect your personal data, such as your ASUS/ROG account ID and browser ID, through these cookies.<br><br>We also use cookies to gather information, such as which ads you’ve seen while using ASUS products and services, to understand your interests. These cookies also play a role in assessing the success of our advertising campaigns, such as Google Ads, Google Double Click and Google Campaign Manager cookies provided by Google Inc. ([https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en)), Twitter Ads by X Corp. ([https://twitter.com/en/privacy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy)), Meta Ads by Meta Platforms, Inc. ([https://www.facebook.com/privacy/policies/cookies](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/policies/cookies)), LinkedIn Ads by LinkedIn Corp. ([https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy)), TikTok Ads by TikTok ([https://www.tiktok.com/legal/page/row/privacy-policy/en](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/page/row/privacy-policy/en)), AWIN pixel by AWIN Ltd ([https://www.awin.com/gb/privacy](https://www.awin.com/gb/privacy)), Criteo tags by Criteo S.A ([https://www.criteo.com/privacy/](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/)) and Quantcast cookies by Quantcast International Limited ([https://legal.quantcast.com/](https://legal.quantcast.com/)). The data collected through these cookies may be shared between ASUS and advertising campaign providers. |
| YouTube cookie | These cookies allow Google to track the record of watching any YouTube videos embedded on our website and service, and to personalize your YouTube browsing experience. Regarding how Google uses the cookies information through YouTube videos, please visit Google’s website at [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en). |

#### 5.2 How to manage cookies settings

(1) You can adjust your cookie settings by going into your browser preferences, visiting the above links introducing third party cookies, or clicking at “Cookie Settings” at the footer of ASUS websites (only applicable in certain countries) where you can choose whether to accept, block, or delete some or all cookies, including third-party cookies.

(2) In certain countries, the first time you visit ASUS websites, you might see a brief introduction on how we use cookies in a banner on these sites. You can decide to accept or block cookies of Section 5.1.(2) through this banner.

(3) If you decide to block cookies, you may not be able to access all features of ASUS products and services.

(4) The options for cookie settings can vary based on the type and version of the browser you use. We have provided information for commonly used browsers below. You can check the links to learn how to manage your cookie settings through these browsers. If you use a different browser or the content in the links is unavailable, please refer to the privacy statements or support pages of those browsers for guidance. You can also visit [https://www.aboutcookies.org/](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) for information on managing your cookie settings across various browsers.

*   How to control your cookies settings in the Google Chrome browser:  
*   How to control your cookies settings in the Microsoft Edge browser:

[https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-edge/view-cookies-in-microsoft-edge-a7d95376-f2cd-8e4a-25dc-1de753474879](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-edge/view-cookies-in-microsoft-edge-a7d95376-f2cd-8e4a-25dc-1de753474879)

*   How to control your cookies settings in the Mozilla Firefox browser:  
    [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored)
*   How to control your cookies settings in the Apple Safari browser:  
    [https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac)

#### 5.3 Web Beacons

A web beacon is a small, usually Invisible graphic (1x1 pixel) In the form of a GIF or PNG image. It’s used on websites or in emails to gauge the success of campaigns. ASUS or our service providers may use web beacons to track if you visit specific pages or click on links in ASUS products and services. For example, we might include web beacons in our marketing emails, such as ASUS newsletters, to see which content you clicked on or read. We’ll use the information gathered from web beacons to enhance our websites and ASUS products and services.

### **6\. Third-party links in ASUS products and services**

**This paragraph explains that if you click on links or use services offered by third parties, it’s important to consistently check the privacy statements provided by those third parties.**

ASUS products and services may have links to websites from other companies. It’s important to note that ASUS is not in charge of the security measures, privacy practices, or content of those other websites. We recommend being cautious when you navigate away from our sites and taking the time to read the privacy statements of those third-party websites. Remember, this Privacy Policy only applies to ASUS products and services.

### **7\. Security** 

**This paragraph describes how ASUS safeguards your personal data and offers tips on how you can protect your own personal data.**

We take steps to safeguard your personal data from unauthorized access, changes, disclosure, or loss. Our internal reviews cover how we collect, store, and process data, and we implement both technical and organizational security measures, as well as physical security measures, to prevent unauthorized access to systems where your personal data is stored.

The transmission of personal data between different ASUS locations and affiliated entities is done through our secure wide area network. Whether you’re submitting your personal data online or offline, it is protected.

Although we do our best, perfect security on the internet cannot be guaranteed by ASUS. To enhance protection against unauthorized access to your personal data, we suggest that you:

#### 7.1 To protect your ASUS/ROG account, for example:

(1) Choose alphanumeric passwords when creating your ASUS/ROG account.

(2) Use your own designated account name and password to log in to your ASUS/ROG account. It is your responsibility to keep this information confidential, and you are solely accountable for all activities under your ASUS/ROG account.

(3) Regularly update the passwords for your ASUS/ROG account.

(4) Contact us immediately if you discover any unauthorized use of your ASUS/ROG account name or password. ASUS may suspend or terminate access to your ASUS/ROG account with the compromised account name/password and remove associated personal data.

#### 7.2 Ensure the security of your products by regularly installing the latest software updates and using tools like virus/spyware scanners.

#### 7.3 If you discover any security or technical vulnerabilities in ASUS products and services, please get in touch with us through the ASUS Product Security Advisory at [https://www.asus.com/securityadvisory/](https://www.asus.com/securityadvisory/ "https://www.asus.com/securityadvisory/").

### **8\. How to manage your personal data**

**If you have any questions or requests regarding your personal data collected by ASUS, you can do the following:**

**(1)** **Log in to your ASUS/ROG account (for viewing or updating your ASUS/ROG account details).**

**(2)** **Visit the ASUS Privacy FAQ for information.**

**(3)** **Manage privacy-related settings on specific ASUS products and services you use.**

**(4)** **Contact us via the “Customer’s Request on Personal Data” interface on the ASUS official website, via email at** [**privacy@asus.com**](mailto:privacy@asus.com) **or by phone.**

#### 8.1 ASUS/ROG account

(1) Make sure to provide accurate, current, and complete personal data in your ASUS/ROG account, so ASUS can offer you the relevant products and services.

(2) You can view and update your ASUS/ROG account details by logging in and editing your account information.

(3) If you want to subscribe or unsubscribe from ASUS emails and notifications featuring ASUS news, latest products, and services, you can adjust the settings by logging into your ASUS/ROG account, navigating to “Subscribe” in the left column, and choosing YES (for subscribe) or NO (for unsubscribe). You can also unsubscribe through the link at the bottom of ASUS emails. If you choose to unsubscribe, please note that it might take approximately two business days to complete the process.

#### 8.2 ASUS products and services

You have the option to decide whether to allow or block the sharing of your personal data with ASUS. You can adjust these settings at any time while using specific ASUS products and services.

#### 8.3 Cookies settings (Please refer to Section 5.2 in this Privacy Policy.)

(1) You have the ability to control cookie settings in the browser you've installed. This includes choosing to accept, block, or delete some or all cookies (such as third-party cookies) or adjusting other settings whenever you want.

(2) If you don't want ASUS to offer you personalized marketing services and advertisements through third-party cookies, you can block or delete these cookies through your browser at any time.

#### 8.4 Contact ASUS to manage your personal data

If you have any questions or requests concerning your personal data in your ASUS/ROG account or any other data collected by ASUS, such as access, correction, download, blocking, or deletion of your personal data, you can contact us through the methods listed below. If you believe ASUS has improperly collected or used your personal data and want to restrict its use under certain circumstances (for example, if you don't want your personal data to be analyzed), you can contact us at any time.

(1) Please visit the ASUS Privacy FAQ at [https://www.asus.com/support/FAQ/1041753](https://www.asus.com/support/FAQ/1041753)

(2) Submit your personal data access/download or deletion requests through “Customer’s Request on Personal Data” interface on ASUS official website at [https://privacy.asus.com/privacy](https://privacy.asus.com/privacy).

(3) Send an email to [privacy@asus.com](mailto:privacy@asus.com) for other personal data-related requests.

(4) Call us using the relevant customer support number listed at [https://www.asus.com/support/callus](https://www.asus.com/support/callus) if you are not sure where to ask personal-data related requests.

#### 8.5 Whenever you use ASUS products and services, we make an effort to ensure the accuracy and safeguard the security of your personal data from accidental or intentional harm. We are committed to addressing your requests related to your personal data; however, there are situations where we may not be able to fulfill your requests, as outlined below:

(1) When mandated or allowed by applicable laws.

(2) For legitimate business reasons.

(3) In cases of excessively repeated requests that demand disproportionate technical efforts and resources.

(4) To avoid potential risks to the privacy of others.

### **9\. Children’s Privacy**

**This paragraph explains that if you are a child, you need to obtain consent from a parent (or guardian) before sharing your personal data with ASUS. If your parent (or guardian) wishes to oversee your personal data, they can refer to the ASUS Privacy FAQ and reach out to us through “Customer’s Request on Personal Data” interface on the official ASUS website, via [privacy@asus.com](mailto:privacy@asus.com), or by phone (see Section 8.4 for details).**

 We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of sixteen (16) or the equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction without parental consent. We encourage parents (or guardians) to actively participate in their child's online activities and interests when using ASUS products and services.

If you are a child, please obtain parental consent before using ASUS products and services. You can only submit your personal data with parental (or guardian’s) consent. Your parent (or guardian) can contact us through the channels listed in Section 8.4 to give consent for processing your personal data, or request access, correction, download, blocking, or deletion of your personal data. For instance, your parent (or guardian) may contact us if they believe ASUS has wrongly collected and used your personal data or if they want to restrict the use of your personal data under certain circumstances (for example, if they don't want your personal data to be analyzed).

### **10\. Sensitive Personal Data**

In our general practices, ASUS will not ask you for sensitive personal data like details about your medical or health records, political, religious, or philosophical beliefs, criminal allegations or convictions, racial or ethnic background, trade union membership, sexual orientation, sexual history, behavior, or genetic data. Kindly avoid providing us with such sensitive personal data.

### **11\. Changes to ASUS Privacy Policy**

We might update our Privacy Policy occasionally, so it's important to regularly check the posted Privacy Policy on our websites. If you access or use our products and services after the Privacy Policy has been changed, ASUS will assume that you agree to the updated Privacy Policy. The latest version of the Privacy Policy will be available on this page, and we may notify you of any significant changes through methods like email if you ever registered your email address with us. You can find the updated time at the bottom of the Privacy Policy page.

### **12\. Contacting Us**

If you have any questions, concerns, comments, or complaints about the Privacy Policy, or if you believe that ASUS has not followed the Privacy Policy, please reach out to us. If you think that we haven't appropriately addressed any issues related to your personal data collected by ASUS, please be aware that you have the right to file a complaint with the government authorities responsible for personal data protection in your country.

**\*Part 2: ASUS EU Data Act Policy:**
--------------------------------------

During your use of ASUS EU products and services, your data (“Product Data”) in connection with ASUS EU product (“Connected Product”) governed by the EU Data Act may be generated. The ASUS EU Data Act Policy (“Data Act Policy”), along with any other data act notices related to specific Connected Product, explains how we perform the obligations as required under the Article 3 (2) of EU Data Act.

Please note that the following information is intended as a general introduction. The descriptions of Product Data vary depending on the nature of each Connected Product, as detailed in the respective product-specific data act notices.

1.Information about type, format and estimated volume of Product Data:

(1) The Connected Product may generate the following type(s) of the Product Data: log information regarding the performance and system status of hardware, firmware and software operated in Connected Product, as well as settings, usage records and interaction with Connected Product.

(2) Product Data may be made available in one of the following format(s): json, txt, SQLite, dmp, etl or any other commonly-used data formats.

(3) The estimated volume of the Product Data is generally indicated in KBs or MBs per data.

2\. Information about whether the Connected Product is capable of generating the Product Data continuously and in real-time: Product Data may be generated continuously in real time, periodically, or based on your instruction.

3\. Information about whether the Connected Product is capable of storing the Product Data on-device or on a remote server, including, where applicable, the intended duration of retention:

(1) The Connected Product may be capable of storing the Product Data on the device and/or a remote server.

(2) Product Data is generally stored for a limited period needed to achieve data processing purposes, or stored until you delete it.

4\. Information about how the user may access, retrieve or, where relevant, erase the Product Data, including the technical means to do so, as well as their terms of use and quality of service:

(1) For Product Data stored on the device, you can access, retrieve and erase it by accessing the relevant folder on the device, as indicated in the data act notice for the respective Connected Product.

(2) For Product Data stored on a remote server, you can access, retrieve and erase it by submitting an application at “Customer’s Request on Personal Data” interface ([https://privacy.asus.com/global/privacy](https://privacy.asus.com/global/privacy)) on ASUS official website.

5\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions, concerns, comments, or complaints about the Data Act, please reach out to us. If you think that we haven't appropriately addressed any issues related to your Product Data generated by Connected Product, please be aware that you have the right to file a complaint with the government authorities responsible for personal data protection in your country.

**ASUSTeK COMPUTER INC.**

Attn: Personal Data Protection Committee

Address: 15, Li-Te Rd., Taipei 112, Taiwan

Email: [privacy@asus.com](mailto:privacy@asus.com)

Updated September/11, 2025 by ASUS Personal Data Protection Committee

###
